yeah that's a real picture kula photo
where that era from Vietnam yeah look
upon Vietnam during the Vietnam War
we want the Leggero and and during when
I was young this was the war now it's in
Syria
my quanto esther alaric esta pasando or
india s lo mismo pyongyang syrian and
someone is shooting at them yeah a year
given the historic pattern and it's a
real it's a real photograph before photo
very rare and next one was the empty
this is a lady just thinking about her
seeds that the most hurtful open
standard basis in media so all of us
have those seeds it does the limited
postpone assisting people to medium I
was in Beirut I'm going to India when I
used to study in India I used to go to
Beirut they planed the cheapest plane
stopped in Beirut
quando just Korea and India pasar por
Vida porque la vie n moderato at the
Escalade and it's a beautiful beautiful
city yet la marea
all white buildings and special trees
Lebanon incinerating College it was
blank of you know they are already
several now it's destroyed everything's
disjoint or India yet to freedom and no
one expected it with the route was like
I don't know like Paris or something it
was very beautiful now I see Martin
evocative of pasado toyota estima see
Istanbul Campari and ADA we all have
those seats those two mimosas of
Fallujah and it doesn't take long for
the situation to change Y muy poco
tiempo losito simple camber the last
comment in America and personal you know
we think our country is very stable the
memos later can replace the moment
earlier but in the last six months we
lost a lot of the
you know pero los últimos a meta para
muchos Libertad a the country was built
by people immigrating because of
religion ll beifuss construir desde
immigrant a religious and now it's not
allowed yo are not permitted if you have
the wrong religion you know the permit
and are seeking a lolly can generally
would be incorrect and the environmental
laws thrown out in in a few months in
3-4 months the many pipelines studying
all the national forests are being
changed much as lays medio ambiente lays
forums SH Odyssey in poco tiempo Sheehan
Geneva Busan dono recursive natural de
Parque platter allocation eCos tree and
Olli adductors and war
yeah just free bomb anybody you know
yeah he never meant impersonal embody
eloquent and the laws controlling the
big banks
Elias que los grandes banco have been
canceled the latest in Martinez contra
de los grandes Valco diaspora quiero so
the reason America in my opinion the
reason America is is prosperous in
opinion
yo creo que estas cosas de prosper yeah
it's because they they used to support
other countries sac Raquel appropriate
asanas Vienna porque estas Unidos a you
dhaba auto spices aunties and the reason
they don't have civil war ii la la causa
por la cual noticed una Guerra civil our
I think is because all all countries
people have been welcome es porque most
olive ammonia a gente que viene mucho
spice and all religion have been
welcomed in lame-o's hola bienvenida
gentle original so the seeds which
created this country y la comida que
creer own octopi
are being destroyed the mystery angle so
no place is safe from your seeds
Ningaloo are at our disposal water to
Samia and you have to understand all of
these things coming from us
it scares a really competent applause
Kasabian dirty and when you think about
that gain at Kentucky marriage equality
reflection CPS eso es lo que significa
to [__] you so Americans like we
cannot blame one person for this problem
nosotros estulin en si no podemos
especial de la culpa una persona pours a
so Luna person approaches problema
coming from me right por que todo esto
viene APO mean I mean if you understand
that she - TSS a compressor you are
protecting yourself and so look at the
protection because you will start making
the seeds porque the corral de its
umbrella people send me so this lady
says she's thinking I also have the
seeds you know I probably I have some
old bad seeds that Syria will come to my
country y esta mujer en esta foto esta
pensando en este en este tipo de cosas
que él pudiera Passarella esta pasando
key Sergio Tengiz semillas Villegas UNT
Guatemala's que podrían general on syria
para me rocks moment and when you
realize all of us have those seeds syria
people are not different from us we are
same we can have cereal here in two
years
todos aquí tenemos la samia's por que su
algo como que esta pasando syria in
those silos and then you came next photo
take refuge yell pensar en esto toma la
fuji a definition of refuge technical
definition life initial Technica the
tomorrow Fujio van toe collusion
to achieve the symbol to put all your
hopes in another person but furnace
depositor todas to Esperanza and not
rapper Sola like your you like your dad
come on como tu papa and the other
person in this case is who teaches you
about seeds ela or persona en este caso
es la personal attack antenna de la
camellia and all of these troubles in
the world coming from us you look to the
rapper sonic at antenna como todos estos
problema del mundo vienen de P then how
does it work
Iike most cases for sure how do we plant
seed comescus unless immediate how can
we stop dancing
what come up with some garment for me
how can we if the world is coming from
me fear elemental mundo en 18 if the
world is coming from my feet
en la meeting me at the moon then I can
control what happens and don't appear to
see a psychopathic controller Lucas's so
we're going to learn that process vamos
a aprender is a process called the four
steps
jemelle cuatro pass then normally people
teach two subjects together normal
mental contains Ania those famous want
oh sorry separately normally when you
hit but I'll throw one is to think about
how much suffering it is if we have to
go to the health or if we have to become
an animal una cancion attends our elsu
free meant ok poder llegar a tener
typical situation when animal oh la
Fiera and then how to protect ourselves
is royal homo protocol Matsumoto process
but he said when you're actually
meditating there are kirijo que cuando
slate and you combine them was
convenient you think about Syria being
safe in Syria and then you think about
refuge it beautiful how to plant a seed
to prevent
Syria in Guadalajara como sembra la
semilla para evitar que tu serais lo que
pasó en Syria in Guadalajara so young
tree young cub Octus avatar dot Megan go
when you meditate you supposed to
combine combine them cuando Morita
look look it la gente que convenors
combined thinking about I don't want I
don't want Syria in my country come be
Natalie I cannot get it but to look at
the person in Syria and 2 pi e and then
think about the seeds how to how to stop
those seeds de pensar and letting me
escape dns captain Bradd para que somos
Fox so during the meditation during this
first meditation we combine those three
photographs red y esta primera metas en
si mas una combinati only Moses tres
Popo graffia first photograph la primera
photography award is la foto de una
Guerra second photograph that's a window
segunda somebody thinking do I have the
seat is it possible in my country Ali
imperiling 70s image was possibly
computing a social medias and if you're
intelligent you have to say yeah it's
possible if he'd given intelligentsia
but yeah la conclusion de que se [__]
any country tank occupied purpose
register America United States North
America can lose half their freedoms in
six months en estado en esto SI ellos
pueden perder lammeter's Libertad
individualism segment then any any
country can do it local cafe services
thanks teacher professor photo it was
hanging on to Gary take refuge or a
south of apartment or [__] you what
message cares I [__] you in Buddhism we
don't believe you can ask Buddha for
special treatment and will it more
Ramos que le puede ver abuddin
please Buddha I heard many people before
but you know let's not let those Karma
open okay
but our ruler with a leap into a new
entrepreneurship into consisting of
elements of Karma's you cannot negotiate
with , nope well they both Caroline so
we have to learn about Karma if you
could be disciplined very good cuddler
danger nietzsche anomalous or top J so
traditionally he said bring your llama
into the room put them on the top of
your head
s tradición de ho en esto text Contreras
Palama DeFelice early knows Pepito
cabeza ask them for understanding para
la casa de comprar Co day to connect
abuse option tired chat song Shi Jin
kingdom come today then put in front of
you all of your teachers
Rojo poner en frente de agosto Metro
Daniela
sources are generally done impedance or
social traffic to talk to some me then
think about how terrible it is if you
have to go down after you type a pencil
or irrigate areas see the photos
converted to Watson training video and
we studied the health other 80s
yesterday more las ocho Infierno and we
studied animal suffering of animals
yes promoters of freemen terrain animal
and the suffering of spirit yes bring in
the high velocity pose very turn Jakarta
to mana candidate senator Koenen then if
you do a good meditation on just like
what it's like to be an animal es capaz
de hacer una y un agua tomatoes tempura
visualizer locate area convert eaten
monuments then automatically you will
you know you want to avoid that
automatic comment a ranganna they a big
knockers Erlanger when you die it's not
that your spirit goes to
I don't know human Arizona this the
worst town I can think of of humor
Arizona see no tectonic rascal Maurice
222 Sabah al merito allocate any
lowercase allocation my credenza and
there's a dog body factory death he was
spiritual service lugar en este lugar y
la fábrica de cuerpo de perro and there
are bad people with long toes with a net
I mean II Ju not personal Val Val acai
pomegranate Varis he not ready and after
you die your soul floating like this
where the cattle where taser that to a
spiritualist a pluton ye and they catch
your soul you know yes collective are
irrelevant to open the dark body gavurin
el cuerpo de perro what you saw in
exponent to all mattes people every
element is not like that king Louis para
nada that's not how you become a dog
Espino s comb of the computer flow
Pharaoh
you have seed in your mind the anusaniya
sentiment right now they are opening
65 per second West Elm is lost intestine
a very endow sympathy no ports a woman
they are creating ahead sanction Iran
Doan Amano my fingers Anne Haran Corrado
cinema novena dent LTC changes he kiss
Amelia's a transformer it become upon se
convierte en una cosa nuestra cama
pata dog's paw H Gaara leg arm a in in
how long does it take cuanto tiempo
completo 160 feet of a second a un
segundo millions representing Konex
since I think huevos a wounded if that's
it that's all you're done then you're
done
whoa whoa it's a domestic American
Pharoah it can happen to anybody the
purpose of what Guerra anytime
what kill momentum it takes a few
minutes
then you're done your country can go to
one in a few days okay you can have a
war here and we can have Syria here and
if you did and not be applicable on
Syria it happens so selling you talked
experience we have we are supporting the
refugees nor Ibrahim Frank talk to her
nosotros estamos are you I'm not a
skilled atheria a given a miracle I do
an alençon again she was having a nice
quiet life in Damascus Jinyoung wannabe
rapper feelin da Moscow she got accepted
to University in Bucharest right yeah
yeah yeah yeah vhe acceptable no
Universiade in bucharest and Ramana then
she went to you know take classes in
Booker you know cephalonia
did suddenly her whole family is in a
refugee camp either a personal computers
for me that's a quantum computer scale
so we have this we have this everybody
has these things okay the remotest
Boston unless they're talking it all
begin okay Decapolis for example in
three more minutes okay the regulated
love I have famous nickname I told
everybody in the world my Mexican
nicknamed senior ultima causa
one more team that to oppose a senior
would be Marco Polo a lot oflot one more
thing a pickup and a chicken
Minoru MTAC chick God and punch ambush
in Japan now let me cook minion so he
gives the example of somebody like a in
against dialect employ a language ending
up on Panda hero and he did some bad
things from the air ok so I was then
they took him to see the into the court
you know they're going to decide he
killed somebody or something and they
take him to the court but for a limit
for practical McNally for Java Holocaust
captain plumbo-jumbo Union do loadable
ki lamb God cancel then if it's most
countries if you have a powerful friend
guanxi Nigeria fighting economical power
also you can ask them you know I got in
some trouble you know can you just you
know do something you know for the play
you don't part of pocket very like that
if you have this kind of powerful person
behind you
pero SI tienes que tipo de persona
Pedrosa opponent you feel relaxed in the
court put cuando vas al food galvatron
kilo means a lot different
Japan non-delegable blue amoeba
pointless and ugly green jobs who shoot
union blow link Eagle take em -
chiba-chiba
so we need a powerful person like that
telephone ami apoyo SOCOM Huerta who is
behind us can query in the court I am
good on the day you die and there will
be a little more because you made many
mistakes in unite porque esto que comer
picked a mucho service and vmss cameo /
oh yeah I like that little gang guy who
made a lot of mistakes
aris kumar pandey here okay committee
muchos Aurora and the day you die gets
more thing you need some powerful guys
kinda messy potamia spoiler of poker who
is that Jean the three jewels la presse
oh yeah
okay and three jewels is not in our
again in Buddhism we don't believe
someone can just okay no problem all
your bad karma is canceled en charisma
not Ramos que si como que alguien Teresa
I won oh yeah
totem our karma can Salado but if you
understand karma per se que es una
comprender karma well una buena
competence like a para so Fran ESO es
como tener un amigo perrault's